你和肯恩啥时候想出的点子啊  太搞笑了
I don't know when you and Jenny worked out that comedy routine, but it was hysterical.
不  那不是计划之中的  那是那个坏家伙想让我难堪
No, that wasn't planned. She was trying to destroy me.
得啦  丽芙  一个可爱的小女孩  才不是想让你难堪呢
[Snorts] Come on, Liv. That sweet little girl was not trying to destroy you.
你们难道没看到橡皮条都被她打断了吗
Did you all not just see the candy cane beat down?
她不择手段就是想让我出丑啊
She was doing absolutely everything she could to make me look bad.
丽芙  你行了吧
Give her a break, Liv.
想想你自己昔日的形象吧
Do you not remember how you were at her age?
绝对不像她一样丧尽天良
I was not a monster like that.
整理衣橱咯  圣诞树还没忙完呢
- I have to go get wardrobe. - Got to work on that tree.
喔喔喔
Ho ho ho.
你应该是最后一个了吧
So you are the last kid on Santa's lap.
让我想想
What are you gonna do?
你要在我身上尿尿  还是喷我一脸口水呢
Pee on me, spit in my face,
要往我衣服里洒奇痒粉  还是把我的眼镜扔到百米开外
pour itching powder down my suit, throw my glasses in the bushes?
小鬼  这些痛苦我今天都经历过了
I have seen it all today, kid.
来吧  你挑一个  早完事早闪人
Just pick one and do it quick.
用我的胡子擦鼻涕  忍无可忍
Blowing your nose in my beard was not an option.
给我走开
Get off of me.
终于来了  帕克
Parker, there you are.
10美元  放到罐子里去  我们赚了多少了
Here's 10 bucks. Add it to the pot. How much did we end up with?
加上这10美元的话  是  是
Including the 10 bucks, that would be... [mouths]
还是10美元
10 bucks.
啥  你一个下午收钱收的手都该抽筋了吧  钱呢
What? They've been handing you money all afternoon. Where did it go?
对不起啦  我是说10美元  还有这个
I'm sorry. I meant 10 bucks and this.
咆哮巨龙直升机
One Screaming Dragon helicopter.
你败光了我们的血汗钱  而且竟然给自己买了个模型飞机
You used all of our Santa money and bought yourself the helicopter?
可不止一个飞机哦  我还收买给那些小孩  我要他们在你身上尿尿  喷你口水
I also paid kids to pee on you, spit in your face,
往你衣服里洒奇痒粉  把你的眼镜扔到百米开外
pour itching powder down your suit, and throw your glasses into the bushes.
为什么  到底是为什么
Why?
因为就在老妈决定给我买模型飞机的时候  你突然跳出来  美梦破碎  你懂的
Because Mom was gonna get that helicopter for me until you wrecked my dream.
这就是报应
Welcome to Christmas revenge.
怎样啊
Ho-ho-how you like me now?
我承受这些该死的痛苦  就是为了给你买圣诞礼物
The only reason I did this Santa stand was so I could pay off your Christmas present.
我费尽心思让妈妈别给你买
I talked Mom out of getting you that helicopter...
是因为我已经买了呀  蠢蛋
Because I already got it for you.
真对不起  没想到你会这么好
I'm sorry, munch. I had no idea you cared.
我也对不起  这就是圣诞吧
Me either. I guess it's just the Christmas spirit.
来吧
Come on.
你抱我纯粹是因为你爱我呢   还是因为你身上尿味十足
Are you hugging me because you love me, or because you're covered in kid pee?
嗯  都是
Mm, why can't it be both?